26th,
I think I'm starting to enjoy the process
old snail bag bro,
but this is still to be fixed here.
ah bro,
but it's that over there,
not live the problem,
but learn from them.
man,
money can't come in if joy has to come out.
Is it on?
it's not what you do,
but who you are,
truth?
I gave 1 quote on motorcycle delivery service,
man,
but very high this cost.
I have no intention of passing on
this for the end customer.
Is it on?
I'm here continuing to make my deliveries,
now fueling 2 seats.
Dude you have no idea how long I've waited
for that moment.
God you're not on?
look at this,
I'll show you,
will I?
not possible,
need to do more advertising campaign
in the Passenger's workshop,
create more ideas to generate more value in the brand,
you know
?